http://www.photomediagroup.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting PhotoMediaOnline.com. The PhotoMedia Group is committed to protecting your privacy.
What our Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy covers any personal information that The PhotoMedia Group obtains from you when you use services on our site. This policy does not cover the practices of companies that The PhotoMedia Group does not own or control, or the actions of people that The PhotoMedia Group does not employ or manage.
Our Privacy Policy may change in the future. We invite you to check back periodically to see if we have made any changes. If we make any material changes, we will post a notice on our home page.
By using this site, you agree to the terms of our policy. For more information about the terms of use for this site, please visit our legal page.
What Personal Information is Collected
Depending on how you use PhotoMediaOnline.com, we may ask you to share personal information with us. Whether you choose to give The PhotoMedia Group information is completely up to you, but keep in mind that if you withhold information, you may not be able to use some of our services.
When Personal Information is Collected
The PhotoMedia Group will ask you for information, including some personal information, if you use one of several services:
Becoming a registered user. In order to register, you need to share some personal information, such as your name and e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to visit The PhotoMedia Group's web pages. But, you will have to register if you want to comment on articles or make full use of our services.
Making a purchase. When you purchase a subscription, you have to supply a billing address, phone number, shipping address, and credit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of PhotoMediaOnline.com
How The PhotoMedia Group Protects Your Information
We realize that our customers trust us to protect their personal information. We take that task seriously. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. For example: We use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") authentication to guarantee the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet help protect your online transaction information from third party interception.
We never display your full credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes.
We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone or share your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.
Unfortunately, despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.
How The PhotoMedia Group Uses Your Personal Information
The PhotoMedia Group collects personal information primarily to make our services more rewarding for you to use. We usually use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences. We may also use your information to contact you for account and promotional purposes. In the event that another company buys the assets or stock of The PhotoMedia Group, your personal information may then belong to another entity.
Who Views Your Personal Information
The PhotoMedia Group may share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, analyzing customer data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, investigating fraudulent activity, conducting customer surveys, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not disclose your personally identifiable information for other purposes. Some personal information is stored on servers owned by other companies. Only The PhotoMedia Group has the right to access this information. We currently share aggregate information about our customers with advertisers and marketing partners. This information does not identify individual users. Personal information may be disclosed if required by law.
The PhotoMedia Group does not currently sell or license personal information. Before selling or licensing your personal information, we will post a notice in this Privacy Policy and on our home page.
At this time, The PhotoMedia Group does not share any personal information with its affiliates. It is possible that this policy will change in the future. If we do decide to share information with our affiliates, we will post a notice in this Privacy Policy and on our home page.
Making a Purchase
When you buy something on PhotoMediaOnline.com. you have to supply a billing address, phone number, shipping address, and credit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of PhotoMediaOnline.com. You can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your credit card number, shipping and billing addresses in the My Account - Profile page.
Children Under 13
Our site is not designed for children. We do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. This policy is designed to protect children. Federal law requires us to take special steps to safeguard children's privacy. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your registration. We will send you a message if we do this. If you are under 13 and want to make a purchase, please ask a parent to place the order for you.
Cookies on PhotoMediaOnline.com
We collect some anonymous information about how you use the site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our web site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave the site. The cookies track your computer, not you. They are not connected to any personal information about you.
Questions About This Policy
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the content or practices of our website, you can contact The PhotoMedia Group directly at:
Stanmeyer Win...
17 Feb, 14
Journalists R...
10 Feb, 14
Rock Photogra...
27 Jan, 14
White House P...
16 Dec, 13
Is Taking Pic...
02 Dec, 13
Most Read
PAST PERSONS OF ...
01 Jun, 12
Steve McCurry: P...
22 Oct, 11
Craig Aurness, 1...
27 Feb, 05
OUR 2011 HONOREE
22 Oct, 11
Hal Eastman: Pho...
Copyright © 2012 PhotoMedia Online. All Rights Reserved.
